[right hand] grasp the green block at the end of the block train | [left hand] stabilize the line of blocks | [right hand] pull the green block away, detaching it from the train
[right hand] place the detached green block on the table to the right | [right hand] reach for the next block in line | [right hand] grasp and detach a small colorful block from the train
[right hand] place the detached block on the table near the green one | [right hand] reach for another block in the train | [right hand] grasp and lift a small block
[right hand] place the block on the table | [right hand] reach for a yellow block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the yellow block
[right hand] place the yellow block on the table | [right hand] reach for a purple block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the purple block
[right hand] place the purple block on the table | [right hand] reach for a yellow block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the yellow block
[right hand] place the yellow block on the table | [right hand] reach for a red block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the red block
[right hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for a green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block
[right hand] place the green block on the table | [right hand] reach for a gray block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the gray block
[right hand] place the gray block on the table | [right hand] reach for a yellow block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the yellow block
[right hand] place the yellow block on the table | [right hand] reach for a green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block
[right hand] place the green block on the table | [right hand] reach for a yellow block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the yellow block
[right hand] place the yellow block on the table | [right hand] reach for a red block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the red block
[right hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for a yellow block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the yellow block
[right hand] grasp and detach the green block from the train | [right hand] place the green block on the table | [left hand] reach for the red and white block | [right hand] reach for the blue block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block
[left hand] grasp and detach the red and white block from the train | [left hand] place the red and white block on the table | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block from the train | [right hand] place the blue block on the table | [right hand] reach for the purple block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the purple block
[right hand] place the purple block on the table | [left hand] reach for the remaining red block in the train | [right hand] reach for the remaining green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block | [right hand] place the green block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the red block | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining blue block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block | [right hand] place the blue block on the table
[left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block | [right hand] place the green block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining blue block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block | [right hand] place the blue block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block | [right hand] place the green block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining blue block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block | [right hand] place the blue block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block | [right hand] place the green block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining blue block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block | [right hand] place the blue block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block | [right hand] place the green block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining blue block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block | [right hand] place the blue block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block | [right hand] place the green block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining blue block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the blue block | [right hand] place the blue block on the table | [left hand] grasp and detach the remaining red block from the train | [left hand] place the red block on the table | [right hand] reach for the remaining green block in the train | [right hand] grasp and detach the green block